Giulio V. Blanc
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Artist Files, 1920-1995, undated, Series 3:; (boxes 1-8; 6 linear ft.)
  - J. Gil Garcia (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition announcement and brochure, 1992 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Photographs and color copy of artwork, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Sergio Garcia (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition catalog, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Victor Manuel Garcia (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1982, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Articles, 1952, 1959 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1969, 1982 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Photographs and photo transparencies, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Enrique Garcia Cabrera (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition brochure, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Nereyda Garcia-Ferraz (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition announcement and newspaper clipping, 1992, 1994 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Juan Carlos Garcia Lavin (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Letter, 1991, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Writings, draft article on Juan Carlos Garcia Lavin by Giulio Blanc, 1991 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition announcements and catalogs, 1988-1991 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Photographs and photo transparency, 1991, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Roberto Garcia York (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Letters, 1980, 1985-1986, 1994, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1978, 1982, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Amparo Garcia (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Writings, draft article on Amparo Garcia by Giulio Blanc, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Antonio Gattorno (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Gattorno, by Ernest Hemingway (copy), 1935 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Florencio Gelabert (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Biographical material and price list, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Newspaper article, 1994 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Julio Girona (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1963 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Charles Gomez (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1982 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Sita Gomez (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Letters and greeting card, 1975, 1989, 1994 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1966, 1981, 1983, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Newspaper articles, 1985, n.d (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Miscellany, large posters, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Victor Gomez (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1982, 1985, 1991 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Photograph and photo transparencies, 1982, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - Lourdes Gomez-Franca (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Letter, 1992 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Writings, poetry by L. Gomez-Franca and book of poems, Era Una Lagrima que Amaba en Silencio, by L. G. Franca, 1975, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1981 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Newspaper articles, 1988, 1993 (Box 3, Reel 5478)
    - Photographs, 1990-1992, undated (Box 3, Reel 5478)
  - José Gomez Sícre (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Pintura Cubana de Hoy (copy), 1944 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Audio material, interview with José Gomez Sícre, audio cassette tape, 1985 [Untranscribed, Spanish] (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Carmelo Gonzalez (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition announcement, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Eladio Gonzalez (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Letters, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition catalogs, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Newspaper clippings and articles, 1972, 1978-1979, 1990 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Miscellany, laser color copies of art work, program for Hacia awards and banquet, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Juan Gonzalez (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Letters, 1980, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Writings, draft writings on Juan Gonzalez by Giulio Blanc and others, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Notes, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1982-1985, 1991 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1974, 1980, 1986, 1991, undated, (3 folders) (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Newspaper clippings and articles, 1980-1992, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Photographs and photo transparencies, 1975-1991 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Miscellany, exhibition list, funeral card in memoriam of Juan Gonzalez, poster, 1981, 1992-1993, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - María Elena Gonzalez (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Letter, 1993 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition announcement, press release, laser copy of artwork, 1994, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Maximiliano Gonzalez (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition announcement and newspaper clippings, 1990, 1992, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Felix Gonzalez-Torres (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Newspaper clippings and articles, 1994, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - José Guerra (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Letter, 1994 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Excerpt from published article, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Ramon Guerrero (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition announcements and catalog, newspaper clipping, 1979, 1987, 1992 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Nicolas Guillen (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Osvaldo Gutierrez (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1944 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Carlos Gutierrez de la Solana (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Alejandro Häsler (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Letter, 1985 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Quisqueya Hernández (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Press release, 1995 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Jorge Hernández Porto (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Julio Hernandez-Rojo (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1981 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1994, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Carmen Herrera (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition announcements and catalogs, 1965, 1985 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Julio Herrera-Zapata (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Ching Ho Cheng (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Biographical material and exhibition announcement, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Horruitiner (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1979 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Elpidio H. Huerta (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition announcements and catalogs, newspaper clippings, 1992, 1994 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - José Iraola (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Letter, 1993 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1993 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Felipe Jimenéz (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1970, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Miguel Jorge (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Letters, 1979-1983 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition announcements and catalogs, 1974, 1983, 1985 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Roberto Juarez (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Writings, draft article on Roberto Juarez by Giulio Blanc, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Carmen Junquera (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Photographs, 1987 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Timour Lam (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1992 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Wifredo Lam (see Appendix for itemized list of printed material) (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Letters, 1944-1946, 1982, 1991-1994, (5 folders) (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Writings, paper on Wifredo Lam by Giulio Blanc and masters paper on Wifredo Lam by Julia P. Herzberg, 1986, undated, (2 folders) (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition and auction announcements and invitations, 1955-1996 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Newspaper clippings and articles (Spanish/English), 1950s-1990s, (3 folders) (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Art Nexus magazine, 1995 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Audio material, interview with Lydia Cabrera on artist Wifredo Lam, audio cassette tape, 1987 [Untranscribed, Spanish] (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Photographs and photo transparencies, 1920s - 1940s, 1970s, undated, (2 folders) (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Miscellany, lists of artwork, catalog raisonne order form, copy of Fata Morgana by André Breton with illustrations by Wifredo Lam [Incomplete], and other material, 1942, 1952, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - María Lamarque (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1936 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Newspaper clippings and articles, 1940, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Victor Patricio Landaluza (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Letter, 1992 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Americas magazine, 1975 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Photo transparency from Sotheby's, 1993 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Armando Lara (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1987 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Julio Larraz (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Greeting card and notes 1988, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition announcements and invitations, 1977-1989, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1979-1992, (2 folders) (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Articles, 1990, 1994 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Photo transparency, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Raquel Lázaro (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1976, undated (Box 4, Reel 5479)
    - Newspaper articles, 1979, 1988 (Box 4, Reel 5479)
  - Lilia Lazo (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements and catalogs, 1982 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Ana León (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1981 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Frank Leon (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1993 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - María Lino (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements and newspaper clippings, 1976-1987 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Silvia Lizama (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1992 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Guido Llinas (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Letter and postcards, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1978, 1981, 1992, 1997 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1953-1955, 1992, 1997 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Connie Lloveras (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements and catalogs, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1994 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Iverna Lockpez (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Letter, 1976 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Omar López (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Letters and postcards, 1994, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Tony López (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1981-1994 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Rolando Lopez-Dirube (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Writings, article on Rolando Lopez-Dirube by Ricardo Pau-Llosa, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition catalogs and invitation, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Article and poster, 1981, n.d (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1980-1981, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Gilberto López-Espina (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1982 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Margarita Lozano (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1978 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Alfredo Lozano (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements and invitations, 1992, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1992 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Carlos Luis (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcement, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Fernando Luis (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1973, 1981, 1986 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1983, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Carlos Luna (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1993 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Laura Luna (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Writings, draft article on Laura Luna by Giulio Blanc, poetry by Laura Luna, 1992, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1988, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1991, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Carlos Macía (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Letters, 1983, 1993, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements and catalogs, 1982-1986, 1997, (2 folders) (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1983 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Photographs, 1983, 1992, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Oscar Magnan (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Matty Marcos (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1975 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Luis Marin (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1993 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Rosario Marquardt (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Letter, 1994 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1989, 1993 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Articles on Rosario Marquardt, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1989-1994, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Raimundo Martin (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcement, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Pedro Martinez (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1944-1951 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Raul Martinez (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition brochure, 1992 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - María Martínez-Cañas (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Letters, 1992 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1989-1995 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1991, 1994 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Luis Martinez-Pedro (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1945-1947, 1989 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Photographs and photo transparencies, 1950, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Julio Matilla (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1957-1958, 1975, 1982 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Roberto Mendez (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Cifra de la Granada, by Roberto Mendez, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Francisco Mendez Diez (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Ana Mendieta (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1981-1993 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1980, 1987 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Articles and press release, 1989, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Manuel Mendive (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1986 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Photograph, 1963 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Margarita de Mena (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1975, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Elia Rosa Mendia (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Glexis Menocal (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Letters, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Narciso Menocal (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Letter, 1994 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Pedro Menocal (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Richard de Menocal (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Postcard to Margherita Blanc, 1980 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1977 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Eduardo Michaelsen (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Writings, essay by Miguel Barnet, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1981, 1989 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Photographs, photo transparencies and negatives, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - José Mijares (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements and brochures, 1992, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1992, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1981, 1994, 1996 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - American Cancer Society magazine, 1980 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Raúl Milían (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1989 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Rafael Mirabal (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1974, 1976 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Ibraham Miranda (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1993 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Antonio Molina (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcement, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Hector Molné (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1994, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1995 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Orlando Monteagudo (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcement and invitation, 1979 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Eduardo Morales (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Notes, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Heriberto Mora Macia (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, 1992, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Letters, 1992 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Writings, draft article on Heriberto Mora Macia by Giulio Blanc, 1992 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1992 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1994 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1993 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Eduardo Moras (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1994 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Rafael Moreno (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Articles, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Clara Morera (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Letter, 1995, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1993 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Esteban Najarro (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1965 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Juan Navarrete (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Juan Nickford (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1984 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Glexis Novoa (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Writings, draft of catalog essay on Glexis Novoa by Giulio Blanc, 1993 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1993 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - William Oberheiser (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1992 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Gustavo Ojeda (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Letters, 1981-1985 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Writings, draft essay on Gustavo Ojeda by Giulio Blanc, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1980-1992 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1987 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Photographs and photo transparencies, 1984-1985, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Juan Martin Oliva (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Postcard, 1994 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition catalog and newspaper clippings, 1994, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Price list, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Photographs and photo transparencies, 1993, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Pedro Pablo Oliva (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1992 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Tomas Oliva (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcement, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Aramis O'Reilly (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1985 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Pedro Ortiz (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1969 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Felipe Orlando (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcement, 1959, 1963 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Miguel Padura (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Notes, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1990, 1994, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Jorge Pantoja (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Letter, 1992 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition catalog, 1992 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1993 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Jorge Pardo (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Letter with accompanying catalog, 1985 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1985 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Manuel Pardo (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Letter, 1986 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Exhibition announcements and poster, 1986 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Press release, 1986 (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Ricardo Pau-Llosa (Box 5, Reel 5480)
    - Letters, 1981-1982, undated (Box 5, Reel 5480)
  - Amelia Peláez (see Appendix for an itemized list of printed material) (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Letter of recommendation from Russian artist, Mm. Alexandra Exter, 1936 (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Writings, proposal for paper on Amelia Peláez by Giulio Blanc, undated (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Notes, 1987, undated (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Exhibition announcements, invitations and brochures, 1988, undated (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1930s-1980s, 1991, (3 folders) (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1920s-1990s, undated, (4 folders) (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Articles on Peláez, 1960s-1990s, undated, (2 folders) (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Poema Deseperado, by Luis Amado Blanco with illustrations by Amelia Peláez, 1937 (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Publications, Museum of Modern Art Bulletin: Modern Cuban Painters, The Metropolitan, 1944, 1978 (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Audio material, interview with Elena Peláez de Medero, audio cassette tape, 1994 [Untranscribed, Spanish] (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Photograph and photo transparency, miscellany, pages of catalog, 1960, undated (Box 6, Reel 5481)
  - Gina Pellon (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Letter, 1983 (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Exhibition announcements and brochures, 1966, 1975-1993, undated (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Exhibition catalogs, 1973-1974, 1979, 1981-1982, undated (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1989, 1996, undated (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Photo transparency and postcards, 1982-1983, undated (Box 6, Reel 5481)
  - Umberto Peña (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Biographical material and exhibition catalog, undated (Box 6, Reel 5481)
  - Julio Antonio Perez (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Exhibition announcements and catalogs, 1992, 1994, undated (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1994 (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 6, Reel 5481)
  - Pedro Perez (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Press release and miscellany, list of artwork and other material, 1983-1985, 1991 (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - News paper clippings, 1993, undated (Box 6, Reel 5481)
  - Marta Maria Perez Bravo (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Biographical material and articles, 1988-1989, undated (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Exhibition announcement and press release, 1994 (Box 6, Reel 5481)
  - Jorge Pérez-Castaño (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Biographical material, undated (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Letters, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Reel 5481)
    - Exhibition announcements and press release, 1979, 1982, 1993 (Box 6, Reel 5481)